evil-comic.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Evil Inc

We do not sell or share any personal information with other companies or any third parties. Below, we would like to detail what information we use, and how we use it.

If you have any comments, questions, or feedback on this policy, please let us know via e-mail.

**Server Logs**

Our Web server does log your IP address and type of web browser in standard server logs. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.

**Cookies**

We use a “session-based” cookie for every user to our website. It helps us store temporary information about you: Preferences you set during your visit. It gets deleted from your machine when you close your browser, and the information associated with it gets deleted within 4 hours of you leaving our site. We use a “permanent” cookie if you are a registered, logged-in user of the site, and opted to have us “Remember Login Info”. This is how we know who you are in the forums, and whether you want email from us (see below). We do not log the cookies in our web server logs.

This site and third-party vendors use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) or other first-party identifiers, and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together.

We use PayPal for purchases from the Evil Inc Store. For information on Paypal’s policy and guidelines, see their privacy policies at: http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside

**Contact & Personal Information**

When you register or buy something from our store, we receive some personal information. This can include name, email address, and shipping address in all sorts of various cases. As we said, we won’t sell this. If you bought something, we simply use it to ship that product to you. If you registered and gave us your email address, we may email you things (the daily strip, the monthly newsletter, etc.), but only if you checked the indicated box when you registered. To uncheck it, so we won’t email you stuff, you can do that at: http://www.evil-comic.com/users/info.html

**Ad Servers**

To help support the site, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

**Opt out**

To learn more or to opt out of targeted advertising [go here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Visitors can opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertiser Features used through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (for example, the NAI’s consumer opt-out). [Here are more opt-outs for Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**Google Advertising Features enabled**

Advertiser Features include Demographics and Interest reporting, Remarketing, GDN Impression Reporting, and the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration.

**Public Forums**

This site makes forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise very high caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. In general, we recommend you don’t.

If you have any comments on the above policies and descriptions, contact us!
